Guide to the Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
- Martin, Damon, Butt Great!, Surrey House, HIS 06990, 1974 (Box 71)
- Martin, Damon, Long Hard Buck, Surrey House, MH 441, 1974 (Box 82)
- Martin, Damon, Butt Bucker, Surrey House, MH 449, 1974 (Box 82)
- Martin, Damon, Cocke Balls, Surrey House, MH 456, 1974 (Box 82)
- Martin, Damon, Butt Boy!, Surrey House, MH 472, 1974 (Box 83)
- Martin, Evan, The Chicken-Hawks, Greenleaf Classics, AC 349, 1985 (Box 23)
- Martin, James, Ballin' In The Spa, Eros Publishing, GYP 102, 1981 (Box 16)
- Martin, James, 14-Year-Old Stud, Star Dist., SPADE 141, 1974 (Box 66)
- Martin, Jock, Put It In!, Surrey House, MH 406, 1973 (Box 81)
- Martin, Jonathan, Soldiers Of Sodom, Brandon House, 6108, 1970 (Box 13)
- Martin, Jonathan, Gay Soldier, Lambda Press, LB 107, 1970 (Box 33)
- Martin, Joseph, Gay And Glad, Spade Publishing, 191, n.d. (Box 58)
- Martin, Kay, The Divorcees, Pyramid Books, F-750, 1962 (Box 53)
- Martin, Rex, The Jaded Boy, Torch Reader, TR-1034, 1971 (Box 87)
- Marvin, Ronn, Mr. Ballerina, MacFadden-Bartell, MB 60-347, 1968 (Box 35)
- Marvin, Ronn, Mr. Ballerina, Regency, RB-103, 1961 (Box 54)
- Marx, Richard, Cockwork Orange, Surrey House, MH 413, 1973 (Box 81)
- Mason, Doug, Brothers-Lovers, Arena, DS 104, 1982 (Box 1)
- Mason, Doug, Brotherly Lust, Arena, DS 106, 1982 (Box 1)
- Mason, Doug, Pumping Jocks, Arena, DS 117, 1983 (Box 1)
- Mason, George, The Coach's Prime Meat, Big Boy Series, BB-103, n.d. (Box 12)
- Mason, Steven, Escort Service, Regency, 1024, 1970 (Box 54)
- Massey, Sam, Return Of The Greek, GX, Inc., SP 108, 1973 (Box 29)
- Massey, Sam, The Strange Ranger, GX, Inc., SP 118, 1973 (Box 29)
- Masters, Jock, Get It In The Rear, Surrey House, HIS 06977, 1974 (Box 71)
- Masters, Simon, The Gay Savages, All Star Books, AS 96, 1966 (Box 1)
- Masters, Simon, The Gay Savages, All Star Novel, AS 96, 1966 (Box 1)
- Maston, Raymond, High Ball Trucker, Arena, MP 109, 1983 (Box 2)
- Maston, Raymond, Big Rod, Arena, PF-120, 1984 (Box 3)
- Maston, Raymond, Shore Leave Hunk, Arena, PF-127, 1984 (Box 3)
- Mathews, Dan, Slave Man, P. E. C., FL 54, 1969 (Box 51)
- Mathews, Matt, Men's Room, Publisher's Consultants, BAB 107, 1978 (Box 49)
- Maugham, Charles, Romeo's Romeo, Nordisk Bladcentral, SVEA 57, 1970 (Box 36)
- Maugham, Robin, The Servant, Avon, AVON 233, 1949 (Box 4)
- Maugham, Robin, The Jungle Of Love, Avon, AVON 695, 1955 (Box 4)
- Maugham, Robin, The Green Shade, Signet Books, T 3214, 1966 (Box 57)
- Maxwell, Sames, Les Enfants Terribles, Continental Classics, CC-118, 1967 (Box 14)
- Mayzk, R. G., Queenstown Court, P. E. C., FL 27, n.d. (Box 51)
- McAlmon, Robert, There Was A Rustling Of Black...., Belmont Books, 92-296, 1963 (Box 6)
- McBride, Scott, Kentucky Stud, Blueboy Library, 80002, 1976 (Box 7)
- McBride, Scott, Man's Country, Blueboy Library, 80014, 1976 (Box 7)
- McBride, Scott, The Pride And The Power, Blueboy Library, 80039, 1977 (Box 8)
- McBride, Scott, Pride, Integrity, Gay, Blueboy Library, 80063, 1977 (Box 9)
- McBride, Scott, Boys For Sale, GX, Inc., SP 113, 1973 (Box 29)
- McBride, Scott, The Angel Of The Alley, GX, Inc., TC 273, 1973 (Box 32)
- McBride, Scott, Hand 'Em Low, Surree House, HIS 69214, 1977 (Box 76)
- McBride, Scott, Blow The Horn, Surree Ltd, HIS 69160, 1976 (Box 73)
- McBride, Scott, Lavender Triangle Murders, Surree Ltd, HIS 69248, 1978 (Box 77)
- McBride, Scott, Devil's Phallus, Surree Ltd, HIS 69253, 1978 (Box 77)
- McBride, Scott, Chicken Ring, Surree Ltd, HIS 69278, 1979 (Box 78)
- McBride, Scott, Bullfight Stud, Surree Ltd, SS 035, 1978 (Box 85)
- McBride, Scott, Hard For The Kid, Surree Ltd, SS 050, 1978 (Box 85)
- McBride, Scott, Young Butt Full, Surrey House, HIS 06998, 1974 (Box 72)
- McCall, Jack, Gay Stud Farm, Eros Publishing, GYP-111, 1983 (Box 16)
- McCandless, Chance, Rock Hard, Surrey House, HIS 06991, 1974 (Box 71)
- McClain, Burt, Gunfighter's Glory, Blueboy Library, 80011, 1976 (Box 7)
- McClain, Burt, Shootout In Cheyenne, Blueboy Library, 80058, 1977 (Box 9)
- McClain, Burt, Cal Jardine, Blueboy Library, 80072, 1977 (Box 9)
- McClain, Burt, Cal Jardine Book Ii, Blueboy Library, 80084, 1977 (Box 10)
- McClain, Burt, Bi-Sex Stud, Surree Ltd, HIS 69234, 1978 (Box 76)
- McCord, Gordon, The Oralist, Eros Publishing, GGS-110, 1974 (Box 16)
- McGraw, Rod, The Singing Wind, Echelon, IL-332, 1968 (Box 15)
- McHenry, David, Hot Nights And Damp Sheets, Valley Circle Pubn., SV 105, 1972 (Box 88)
- McHenry, John, Queen Of Pleasure, Phenix Publishers, PR 262, 1970 (Box 45)
- McKay, Travis, Love Mouth, Eros Publishing, GGS-108, 1974 (Box 16)
- Mclean, Curt, Brother Gay, Greenleaf Classics, AC 126, 1976 (Box 21)
- McLean, Eric, Slaves And Lovers, GX, Inc., SB 603, 1974 (Box 28)
- McMann, Butch, His Cocky Son, Star Dist., SS-1036, 1979 (Box 67)
- Meadows, Jim, Arab Slave Boys, Parisian Press, P215, 1972 (Box 91)
- Melburn, Jonathan, Billy Stud, Greenleaf Classics, AC 105, 1975 (Box 20)
- Mellman, Larry, The Sin Of Socrates, Global Press, FGL 20, 1970 (Box 38)
- Mergendahl, Charles, The Bramble Bush, Bantam Books, F1968, 1958 (Box 5)
- Merrick, Gordon, One For The Gods, Avon, 0-380-01435-1, 1971 (Box 3)
- Merrick, Gordon, Forth Into Light, Avon, 0-380-35782-8-225, 1974 (Box 3)
- Merrick, Gordon, Forth Into Light, Avon, 380-17251-175, 1974 (Box 3)
- Merrick, Gordon, An Idol For Others, Avon, 0-380-00971-4, 1977 (Box 3)
- Merrick, Gordon, Now Let's Talk About Music, Avon, 0-380-77867-X-295, 1981 (Box 3)
- Merrick, Gordon, The Quirk, Avon, 0-380-38992-4-225, 1978 (Box 4)
- Merrick, Gordon, Perfect Freedom, Avon, 0-380-80127-2-395, 1982 (Box 4)
- Merrick, Gordon, The Lord Won't Mind, Avon Books, 0-380-01404-1, 1970 (Box 95)
- Merrill. James, The (Diblos) Notebook, Popular Library, 60-2155, 1965 (Box 48)
- Merritt, Daniel, Brothers, Numbers, 10019, 1978 (Box 37)
- Michael, Jay, The Boys In The Barn, Surree House, MH 468, 1974 (Box 82)
- Michael, Jay, Rump Rider, Surrey House, HIS 69101, 1974 (Box 72)
- Michael, Jay, Do It Up Brown, Surrey House, MH 458, 1974 (Box 82)
- Michaels, Bob, Hunky Roommates, Surree Ltd, HIS 69246, 1978 (Box 77)
- Michaels, Bob, Inside Man, Surree Ltd, MH 495, 1979 (Box 83)
- Michaels, Jack, Homo In The Guesthouse, Brandon House, 2081, 1968 (Box 12)
- Michaels, Jay, The Hungry Boys, I, Surree Ltd, SS 047, 1978 (Box 85)
- Michaels, Jay, The Hungry Boys Ii, Surree Ltd, SS 051, 1978 (Box 86)
- Michaels, Phil, The Naive Homosexual, Brandon House, 3065, 1969 (Box 12)
- Michaels, Ward, Silver Summer, Arena, GB 106, 1978 (Box 2)
- Michaels, Ward, Silver Screen, Arena, GB 112, 1978 (Box 2)
- Michaels, Ward, Twins, Arena, GB 123, 1979 (Box 2)
- Michaels, Ward, Star Struck, Arena, GB 120, 1978 (Box 2)
- Michaels, Ward, Locker Room Lovers, Eros Publishing, GYP-107, 1982 (Box 16)
- Michaels, Ward, Cocky Cruiser, Surree Ltd, HIS 69154, 1975 (Box 73)
- Michaels, Ward, Ream The Team!, Surree Ltd, HIS 69162, 1976 (Box 74)
- Michaels, Ward, Meat Man, Surree Ltd, HIS 69199, 1977 (Box 75)
- Michaels, Ward, Farm Boys, Surree Ltd, HIS 69221, 1977 (Box 76)
- Michaels, Ward, Suck Slave, Surree Ltd, HIS 69232, 1978 (Box 76)
- Michaels, Ward, Horny For Hardhats, Surree Ltd, SS 031, 1976 (Box 85)
- Milano, Chris, Brawny, Hamilton House, RAM 10-110, 1975 (Box 33)
- Miller, Charlotte, Hannibals Retreat, Spartan Books, SB 1021, 1972 (Box 91)
- Miller, H. D., I Love Thee Beast, MacFadden-Bartell, MB 75-173, 1966 (Box 35)
- Miller, Marcus, Locker-Room Lovers, Corinth Pubns., LB 1212, 1967 (Box 14)
- Miller, Marcus, A Masculine Scent, Corinth Pubns., NB 1859, 1967 (Box 14)
- Miller, Marcus, Boy Meets Boy, Corinth Pubns., NB 1880, 1968 (Box 14)
- Miller, Marcus, Gay Twins, Greenleaf Classics, AB 435, 1968 (Box 20)
- Miller, Marcus, Gay Safari, Greenleaf Classics, AB 438, 1968 (Box 20)
- Miller, Marcus, Darling Boy, Greenleaf Classics, AB 444, 1968 (Box 20)
- Miller, Marcus, Captive In Lavender, Greenleaf Classics, AB 448, 1968 (Box 20)
- Miller, Marcus, Fruit Punch, Greenleaf Classics, AB 455, 1968 (Box 20)
- Miller, Marcus, Carry On, Charlie, Phenix Publishers, CB 548, 1967 (Box 43)
- Miller, Marcus, The Gay Swap, Phenix Publishers, CB 554, 1968 (Box 43)
- Miller, Marcus, The Mother Truckers, Phenix Publishers, CB 558, 1968 (Box 43)
- Miller, Marcus, Gay Stud, Phenix Publishers, LL 736, 1967 (Box 44)
- Miller, Marcus, Gay Revolution, Phenix Publishers, PR 218, 1969 (Box 44)
- Miller, Marcus, Copsucker, Phenix Publishers, PR 258, 1970 (Box 45)
- Miller, Marcus, Hustle, Phenix Publishers, PR 267, 1970 (Box 45)
- Milton, Jack, Queens Of The Road, Brandon House, 6096, 1970 (Box 13)
- Mimms, Smokey *, Highway Humpers, Rough Trade, RT 436, n.d. (Box 55)
- Mimms, Smokey, Tough Biker Turf, Star Dist., SS-1004, n.d. (Box 66)
- Minor, Jack, Jimmy's First Time, Rough Trade, RT 409, n.d. (Box 54)
- Minor, Jack, Pumping Rookie, Rough Trade, RT 417, n.d. (Box 54)
- Mishima, Yukio, Forbidden Colors, Avon, 380-00183-125, 1968 (Box 4)
- Mitchell, Carl, Walk The Gay Night, Triumph, TNC 312, 1967 (Box 87)
- Monette, Paul, Taking Care of Mrs. Carroll, Avon Books, 45161, 1978 (Box 91)
- Montague, Murray, Security Risk, Blueboy Library, 80000, 1976 (Box 7)
- Montague, Murray, The Damocles Conspiracy, Blueboy Library, 80009, 1976 (Box 7)
- Montague, Murray, My Man David, Blueboy Library, 80021, 1976 (Box 7)
- Montague, Murray, The Trouble With Peter, Blueboy Library, 80025, 1977 (Box 8)
- Montague, Murray, Yesterday's Closet, Blueboy Library, 80036, 1977 (Box 8)
- Montague, Murray, Cod Pieces, Blueboy Library, 80049, 1977 (Box 8)
- Montague, Murray, The Other Side Of Love, Blueboy Library, 80057, 1977 (Box 9)
- Montague, Murray, The Acapulco Affair, Blueboy Library, 80066, 1977 (Box 9)
- Montague, Murray, The Yearning Point, Blueboy Library, BB 107, 1978 (Box 11)
- Montague, Murray, Peter's Problem, Blueboy Library, NIL 109, 1978 (Box 37)
- Montague, Murray, My Man David, Numbers, NIL 107, 1978 (Box 37)
- Montague, Murray, Thar He Blows!, Surey Books, AGR 106, 1983 (Box 68)
- Montague, Murray, Hardhat Fever, Surree Ltd, HIS 69205, 1977 (Box 75)
- Montgomery, Rex, Rough Ridin', Blueboy Library, 80054, 1977 (Box 9)
- Montgomery, Rex, Man-Made Stud, Surree Ltd, HIS 69217, 1977 (Box 76)
- Moore, Gordon, Night Hawk, GX, Inc., TC 272, 1973 (Box 32)
- Moore, Marlon, Black Trade, Star Dist., HS 128, n.d. (Box 62)
- Moore, Martin, Undercover, Blueboy Library, 80006, 1976 (Box 7)
- Moore, Martin, To Dare To Be Different, Blueboy Library, 80031, 1977 (Box 8)
- Moore, Martin, The Price Of Pride, Blueboy Library, 80046, 1977 (Box 8)
- Moore, Martin, To Dare To Be Different, Blueboy Library, NIL 115, 1977 (Box 37)
- Moore, Martin, Hot Cop's Buns, Surree Ltd, HIS 69241, 1978 (Box 77)
- Moore, Robin, Aloha, Manor Books, 532-19133, 1976 (Box 36)
- Mordell, Daniel, Big Rod, Surrey House, HIS 69186, 1976 (Box 74)
- Morgan, Helene, Queer Daddy, Satan Press, 101, 1965 (Box 57)
- Morgan, Kenneth, Going Gay, N. P. Inc., 6012, 1969 (Box 36)
- Moritzen, Nils, I Am Curious (Gay), Numbers, 10013, 1978 (Box 37)
- Moro, Manny, King Of The Docks, Rough Trade, RT 472, n.d. (Box 56)
- Morrison, Ed, Big Mouthful, Surrey House, HIS 69102, 1974 (Box 72)
- Morrison, Gilbert, Touch And Down, F.S. Publishing, GW 110, n.d. (Box 18)
- Morrow, Russ, Cocked Up, Surrey House, HIS 06943, 1972 (Box 70)
- Morton, Herb, Gay And Happy, Paramount, SL 516, 1971 (Box 40)
- Mosher, W. F., Other Than A Man, Echelon, IL-241, 1968 (Box 15)
- Moute, Alex, The Rough Trade, Valley Circle Pubn., SV 109, 1972 (Box 88)
- Mullen, Ron, Trucker Fucker, Rough Trade, RT 478, 1979 (Box 56)
- Munves, Alain, I, A Homosexual, Collectors Publications, -0-, 1969 (Box 14)
- Murphy, Dennis, The Sergeant, Fawcett, S 291, 1958 (Box 17)
- Murphy, Dennis, The Sergeant, MacFadden Books, 75-201, 1958 (Box 91)
- Murphy, Jeff, Door-To-Door Chicken, Surrey House, HIS 06972, 1973 (Box 71)
- Murphy, Phil, Newcomer, Surrey House, HIS 06947, 1973 (Box 70)
- Murray, Gene, Gang-Bang Bikers, Surree Ltd, HIS 69176, 1976 (Box 74)
- Murray, Michael, Brothers, Rough Trade, RT 422, n.d. (Box 54)
- Myers, Grant, The Farmer's Son, Star Dist., SPADE 015, 1973 (Box 65)
- Naar, Marty, Rough Rider, Rough Trade, RT 479, 1979 (Box 56)
- Nemec, John, The Spy Who Came To Bed, Triumph, TNC 319, 1968 (Box 87)
- Newbury, Call Boy, Monarch Books, 226, 1961 (Box 36)
- Newhouse, John, The Diary Of The Gay Casanova, Nordisk Bladcentral, SVEA 36, 1969 (Box 36)
- Newman, Alan, Glory Hole, Rough Trade, RT 452, n.d. (Box 55)
- Nielson, Grant, The One that Counts, Greenleaf Classics, Inc., GL129, 1969 (Box 94)
- Nielson, Scott, Man In The Middle, Eros Publishing, GGS-111, 1974 (Box 16)
- Niles, Blair, Strange Brother, Avon, AVON 493, 1931 (Box 4)
- Niles, Blair, Strange Brother, Avon, AVON 407, 1952 (Box 95)
- Nita, Brian, Stick Shift, Publisher's Consultants, BAB 104, 1978 (Box 49)
- Nitzer, Dr. Rodney, Gay Lovers: Hard Men With Hard Bodies, Proctor File Illus., PF-1007, n.d. (Box 49)
- Nitzer, Robert, Brother Humper, Rough Trade, RT 404, n.d. (Box 54)
- North, Gene, Boy On The Block, Barclay House, 7076, 1969 (Box 6)
- North, Gene, Good-Bye, Gay Love, Greenleaf Classics, AB 446, 1968 (Box 20)
- North, Gene, Extra Man, Pendulum Books, 0-433, 1970 (Box 43)
- North, Gene, Daddy's Boy, Phenix Publishers, CB 556, 1968 (Box 43)
- North, Gene, Skid Row Sweetie, Phenix Publishers, LL 767, 1968 (Box 44)
- North, Gene, Holy Grope, Spartacus Books, SB-106, 1975 (Box 17)
- North, Gene, Travel Leather, Spartacus Books, SB-110, 1976 (Box 17)
- O'Day, Patrick, Jock House, Timely Books, -0-, 1971 (Box 91)
- O'Hara, Brian, Semper Fidelis, Blueboy Library, BB 105, 1978 (Box 11)
- O'Shea, Sean, Whisper, Softcover Library, 904X, 1965 (Box 58)
- Onstott, Kyle, The Tattooed Road, Fawcett, D 422, 1960 (Box 17)
- Opton, Buck, Colorado Blue, GX, Inc., SP 102, n.d. (Box 28)
- Ortega, Ralph, Bare Sahara, GX, Inc., SP 115, 1973 (Box 29)
- Ortega, Ralph, Stud Bust, GX, Inc., TC 241, n.d. (Box 31)
- Packer, Vin, Whisper His Sin, Fawcett, 426, 1954 (Box 17)
- Packer, Vin, The Girl On The Best Seller List, Fawcett, S 976, 1960 (Box 17)
- Pannard, Barth *, Boot Licking Slave, Rough Trade, RT 434, n.d. (Box 55)
- Paris, Orlando, The Short Happy Sex Life Of Stud Sorrell, Greenleaf Classics, GC 330, 1968 (Box 24)
- Park, Barry, Cut Loose--Pretty Boy, XXX Inc., GW 122, 1971 (Box 18)
- Park, Jordan, Half, Lion Books, 135, 1953 (Box 34)
- Park, Jordan, Valerie, Lion Books, 153, 1953 (Box 34)
- Parkhurst, Peter, Some Like It Hard, Parisian Press, P 242, 1972 (Box 42)
- Parnay, Evan, Stud Seeker, Star Dist., Club 111, 1973 (Box 59)
- Patcher, E. E., Yesterday's Trade, GX, Inc., TC 216, n.d. (Box 30)
- Patcher, E. E., Yesterday's Trade, Publisher's Consultants, LR 105, 1977 (Box 50)
- Patterson, Art, Trucker Sucker, Surrey House, HIS 06986, 1974 (Box 71)
- Patterson, Art, Buttrustle!, Surrey House, MH 444, 1974 (Box 82)
- Patterson, Haywwod, Scottsboro Boy, Bantam Books, H2357, 1950 (Box 5)
- Paul, Harry, Eat My Money Maker, Surrey House, HIS 06950, 1973 (Box 70)
- Paul, Leslie, Secret Homosexual Compulsions, Classic Pubns., NT 875, 1969 (Box 13)
- Peale, Billy, Climax At Bull Run, Greenleaf Classics, PR 331, 1971 (Box 47)
- Peale, Billy, Coming Out...West, Phenix Publishers, PR 273, 1970 (Box 46)
- Pearl, Jack, Stockade, Pocket Books, Inc., 75133, 1964 (Box 95)
- Pederson, Lyn, Do My Thing, GX, Inc., TC 218, n.d. (Box 30)
- Penn, Ronald, Hungup Hunk, Surree Ltd, HIS 69202, 1977 (Box 75)
- Pepper, Bob, Basket Kissing Cousin, Timely Books, -0-, 1971 (Box 87)
- Pepper, Peter, Two Aginst The World, Encounter Books, EE 105, 1978 (Box 16)
- Pepper, Peter, Cumming Of Age, Janus Studios, DN-120, 1978 (Box 33)
- Pepper, Peter, Big Dick, Surree Ltd, HIS 69151, 1975 (Box 73)
- Pepper, Peter, In Tight Twins, Surree Ltd, HIS 69156, 1975 (Box 73)
- Pepper, Peter, Hot Butt Eater, Surree Ltd, HIS 69165, 1976 (Box 74)
- Pepper, Peter, Hard Driver, Surree Ltd, HIS 69171, 1976 (Box 74)
- Pepper, Peter, Peter Standing, Surree Ltd, SS 012, 1975 (Box 84)
- Pepper, Peter, Good Head, Uncle!, Surree Ltd, SS 013, 1975 (Box 84)
- Pepper, Peter, Hot For Peter, Surree Ltd, SS 029, 1976 (Box 85)
- Pepper, Peter, Hot-Rocks Hotel, Surree Ltd, SS 053, 1979 (Box 86)
- Pepper, Peter, Me And Dick, Surrey House, HIS 06919, 1972 (Box 69)
- Pepper, Peter, The Brass Cock, Surrey House, HIS 06944, 1972 (Box 70)
- Pepper, Peter, Hot Buns, Surrey House, HIS 06970, 1973 (Box 71)
- Pepper, Peter, Prime Meat, Surrey House, HIS 06992, 1974 (Box 71)
- Pepper, Peter, Dick And Peter, Surrey House, HIS 69110, 1974 (Box 72)
- Pepper, Peter, Big Red Waggin', Surrey House, HIS 69113, 1974 (Box 72)
- Pepper, Peter, Turn The Other Cheeks, Surrey House, HIS 69121, 1974 (Box 72)
- Pepper, Peter, Ream-Riders, Surrey House, HIS 69136, 1975 (Box 73)
- Pepper, Peter, Big Jock, Surrey House, HIS 69138, 1975 (Box 73)
- Pepper, Peter, Meatslinger, Surrey House, MH 440, 1974 (Box 82)
- Pepper, Sarge, The Wising Up, GX, Inc., TC 245, 1972 (Box 31)
- Perkins, Michael, Evil Companions, Essex House, 0109, 1968 (Box 95)
- Perry, Troy D, The Lord Is My Shepherd..., Bantam Books, 0-553-07639, 1972 (Box 5)
- Peters, Charlie, Alltime Hard, Surrey House, HIS 06955, 1973 (Box 70)
- Peters, Charlie, Schooltime Hard, Surrey House, HIS 06987, 1974 (Box 71)
- Peters, Charlie, Chicken Chaser, Surrey House, HIS6995, 1974 (Box 91)
- Peters, Fritz, Descent To Darkness, Berkley, D2005, 1952 (Box 11)
- Peters, Fritz, The World At Twilight, Lancer, 73-428, 1964 (Box 34)
- Peters, John, Trickin's Easy, Arena, MP 127, 1984 (Box 3)
- Peters, Norm, Truck Stop Slave, Arena, PF-147, 1985 (Box 3)
- Peters, Norm, Homo Hang Up, Arena, PF-159, 1986 (Box 3)
- Peters, Sal, Sucked Into Success, Star Dist., SPADE 134, 1973 (Box 66)
- Peyrefitte, Roger, Diplomatic Diversions, Panther, 657, 1953 (Box 87)
- Phillips, Rick, Hard: To Take, Surrey House, HIS 06924, 1972 (Box 69)
- Phillips, Rick, The Cop On 69th Street, Surrey House, MH 427, 1973 (Box 81)
- Phillips, Thomas Hal, A Bitterweed Path, Avon, T-83, 1949 (Box 5)
- Phillips, Thomas Hal, Bitterweed Path, Rinehart Books, Inc., T-273, 1949 (Box 93)
- Pichette, Roland, Cycle Slaves, Star Dist., SPADE 118, 1973 (Box 65)
- Pines, Philip, Greek Initiation, Surrey House, HIS 69119, 1974 (Box 72)
- Pines, Philip, Come Cleaner, Surrey House, HIS 69127, 1974 (Box 72)
- Pines, Philip, Hard On His Tail, Surrey House, MH 462, 1974 (Box 82)
- Pines, Philip, Cocksure Coach, Surrey House, MH 475, 1975 (Box 83)
- Pines, Philip, The Sergeant's Privates, Surrey House, MH 479, 1975 (Box 83)
- Plagemann, Bentz, The Steel Cocoon, Crest Books, s347, 1958 (Box 91)
- Platt, Jack, Lessons, Rough Trade, RT 420, n.d. (Box 54)
- Platt, John, Cock Cult, Rough Trade, RT 403, n.d. (Box 54)
- Poindexter, Felix, Stud Ranch, CAJ, -0-, 1969 (Box 13)
- Pomeroy, Pat, Navy Blown, Star Dist., SS-1032, 1979 (Box 67)
- Porter, Dan, Ship Of Queens, Phenix Publishers, PR 224, 1969 (Box 44)
- Porter, Darwin, Butterflies In Heat, Manor Books, 532-19112, 1976 (Box 36)
- Porter, Philip, Fire Island Follies, Greenleaf Classics, GL 104, 1969 (Box 25)
- Powell, Brad, Humpin' Jumpmaster, GX, Inc., TC 212, n.d. (Box 29)
- Powell, Brad, Humpin' Jumpmaster, Publisher's Consultants, GY 102, 1977 (Box 50)
- Powell, Brad, Shadow On The Sand, XXX Inc., GW 115, 1971 (Box 18)
- Powell, Mason, The Brig, Alternate Publishing, -0-, 1984 (Box 93)
- Powell, Ryan, Studsucker, Surrey House, HIS 69107, 1974 (Box 72)
- Powers, Brad, Little Big Horny, GX, Inc., TC 211, n.d. (Box 29)
- Powers, Brad, Little Big Horny, Publisher's Consultants, GY 102, 1977 (Box 50)
- Preston, Harry, Confessions Of A Closet Queen, Academy Press, OAP 9670, 1974 (Box 1)
- Preston, John, Golden Years, Alyson, -0-, 1984 (Box 1)
- Preston, John, Secret Dangers, Alyson, -0-, 1986 (Box 3)
- Price, Larry, The Gay Rebels, Unique, -0-, 1966 (Box 88)
- Prince, Mike, Big Mack, Star Dist., SS-1022, 1979 (Box 67)
- Princeton, Sterling, Ten Inch Tease, Publisher's Consultants, BAB 101, 1978 (Box 49)
- Prinz, Evan, Any Sex Will Do, All Star Books, AS 66, 1965 (Box 1)
- Proctor, Dr., Group Sex: Orgies For Male Lovers, Proctor File Illus., PF-1001, n.d. (Box 49)
- Proctor, Dr., About Animalism: Anals Desire In....., Proctor File Illus., PF-1002, n.d. (Box 49)
- Proctor, Dr., Gay Relations: The More...The Merrier, Proctor File Illus., PF-1009, n.d. (Box 49)
- Proctor, Dr., Gay Rape: Forced Sexual Acts, Proctor File Illus., PF-1010, n.d. (Box 49)
- Proctor, Dr., Gay Performers: Gay Sex In The Public Eye, Proctor File Illus., PF-1011, n.d. (Box 49)
- Proctor, Dr., The Gay Life: Love A Different Way, Proctor File Illus., PF-1004, n.d. (Box 49)
- Prodde, Lance, Caribbean Sex, Parisian Press, P 231, 1972 (Box 42)
- Proferes, J. J., Navy Blues, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1966 (Box 27)
- Proferes, J. J., Hellbound In Leather, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1966 (Box 27)
- Proferes, J. J., Of Hot Nights And Damp Beds, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1966 (Box 27)
- Proferes, J. J., Of Greenbacks And Dress Blues, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1967 (Box 27)
- Proferes, J. J., Weep No More, My Laddie, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1967 (Box 27)
- Proferes, J. J., Guidebook To Sexual Positions Between..., Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1970 (Box 27)
- Proferes, J. J., Hey There Orgy Boy, Guild Press Ltd., RC 102, 1971 (Box 27)
- Proferes, J. J., Cross Country Orgy, Guild Press Ltd., TC 102, 1971 (Box 27)
- Proferes, J. J., The One-Way Street, Guild Press Ltd., TC101, 1968 (Box 28)
- Proferes, J. J., Weep No More, My Laddie, Guild Press Ltd., TC112, 1969 (Box 28)
- Proferes, J. J., Prison Punk, Guild Press Ltd., TC115, 1969 (Box 28)
- Proferes, J. J., Any Man Is Fair Game, Guild Press Ltd., TC121, 1969 (Box 28)
- Proferes, J. J., "John", Guild Press Ltd., TC124, 1969 (Box 28)
- Proferes, J. J., Sex Adventures, Guild Press Ltd., RC 117, 1971 (Box 28)
- Proferes, J. J., Barracks Orgy, Guild Press Ltd., RC 111, 1971 (Box 28)
- Proferes, J. J., Swap Out, Guild Press Ltd., RC 123, 1971 (Box 28)
- Proferes, J. J., GAY COMPANY-69th BATTALION, Guild Press Ltd., RC 133, 1972 (Box 28)
- Proud, Peter, Humpy Highschooler, Surree Ltd, MH 492, 1978 (Box 83)
- Pruyn, Leonard, World Without Women, Fawcett, S 975, 1960 (Box 17)
- Pulanski, Gary, My Cousin..My Lover, Blueboy Library, 80081, 1977 (Box 10)
- Pulsing, Fred, Whipped Cream, Publisher's Consultants, BAB 103, 1978 (Box 49)
- Purdy, James, Eustace Chisholm And The Works, Bantam Books, N3797, 1967 (Box 5)
- Queneau, Raymond, Zazie, Bantam Books, SY4074, 1960 (Box 5)
- Quinn, Paul, Pot & Pansies, Greenleaf Classics, GL 105, 1969 (Box 25)
- Raborg, Frederick, Gin Street Rhythms, Greenleaf Classics, PR 339, 1971 (Box 47)
- Raborg, Frederick, The Judas Match, Greenleaf Classics, PR 354, 1972 (Box 47)
- Raborg, Frederick, Jail Rape, Greenleaf Classics, PR 369, 1972 (Box 48)
- Raborg, Frederick, Gay Vigilante, Greenleaf Classics, PR 357, 1972 (Box 48)
- Raborg, Frederick, Badass Boys, Greenleaf Classics, GN413, 1973 (Box 91)
- Raines, Phil, Within You Without You, Numbers, NIL 102, 1978 (Box 37)
- Raines, Tom, Hard-Corps Slave, Surree Ltd, SS 018, 1976 (Box 84)
- Raines, Tom, Stud-Sucker, Surree Ltd, SS 027, 1976 (Box 85)
- Raji, Mohammad, Truck Stop Torment, Rough Trade, RT-506, 1982 (Box 91)
- Rammer, Rod, Cockpit Cruiser, Surrey House, HIS 06974, 1973 (Box 71)
- Ramp, James H., The Love Smeller, Fanfare Pubn., -0-, 1966 (Box 17)
- Ramp, James H., Wild Strawberry Patch, Fanfare Pubn., -0-, 1966 (Box 17)
- Ramp, James H., A Far Country, Fanfare Pubn., -0-, 1967 (Box 17)
- Ramp, James H., Consenting Adult, Fanfare Publications, -0-, 1967 (Box 93)
- Rand, Lou, The Gay Detective, Saber Books, SA-18, 1961 (Box 57)
- Rand, Lou, Rough Trade (Original Title: Gay Detective), Argyle Book Co., 54-821, 1964 (Box 91)
- Randall, Kirk, Shore Leave, Hamilton House, RAM 10-106, 1974 (Box 32)